好吧  罗斯
Okay, Ross.
我知道你不想进来看到这个
I realize that you didn't expect to walk in and see that, but...
听我解释好吗
Let me explain, okay?
我们什么都没做
We weren't doing anything!
瑞秋  他看到了
Rach, he just saw us.
但你所看到的
But what you saw,
就是全部了
that is the extent of it, okay?
仅仅一个吻而已
One kiss.
不  你说谎我们在巴巴多斯就吻过了
No, come on. That's a lie! We also kissed in Barbados.
哥们儿  闭嘴
Dude, chill!
好吧  我们在巴巴多斯也吻过
Okay, we also kissed in Barbados...
可我们没想那样
...but we didn't plan it. Ok?
发生这件事的唯一原因
The only reason that that happened...
是我看见你吻查莉了
...was because I saw you kiss Charlie.
对  是你开始的  我真的该闭嘴
Yeah, you started it!  I have got to chill.
好吧  我们或许应该
Look, we probably should
在事情发生之前跟你说
have talked to you about this before it ever happened.
可是...
But....
我们也感到非常抱歉  罗斯
Oh, we feel so terrible about this, Ross.
是  可它确实发生了
Yeah. But it did happen.
所以...
So...
罗斯
Ross?
干脆把门关了算了
Can we just close the door?
《老友记》  第十季  第2集 罗斯不难过
Friends S10E02 The One Where Ross Is Fine
罗斯  说点什么
Ross, say something.
什么都行
Anything.
所以说你们俩...
So you two are...?
-是  -是
- Yeah. - Yeah.
那你们有没有...
And have you had...?
-没...  -没...
- No... - No...
可如果我没进来的话  你们会不会...
But if I hadn't walked in here, would you...?
也许...不  不会
Probably--No. No.
罗斯  我们本来没想
Ross, this is not how we wanted you
让你以这种方式发现
to find out about this.
你有权利抓狂
You have every right to go nuts.
我不会抓狂的
I'm not going nuts.
你看我抓狂了
Do you see me going nuts?
不  可你知道我的意思
No, but you know what I mean.
如果你们俩开心...
If you two are happy...
那我也会为你们开心
...then I'm happy for you.
我没事
I'm fine.
-真的  -当然
- Really? - Absolutely.
我没事
I'm fine.
完全没事
Totally fine.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why it's coming out
我的声音又大又尖
all loud and squeaky...
不过说真的  我没事
...because, really, I'm fine.
我不是说看见你们接吻
I'm not saying I wasn't a little surprised
一点也不吃惊
to see you guys kissing.
我是说  开始我有点...
I mean, at first I was like:
不过现在  给我时间消化了
But now that I've had time to absorb it...
喜欢了
Loving this.
-罗斯  -都解决了
- Ross. - It's all working out.
我和查莉  还有你们俩
Me and Charlie. And you two.
知道我们应该干什么吗
You know what we should do?
冷静下来
Calm ourselves?
不
No.
我们应该一起吃顿饭
We should all have dinner.
对  我们明天晚上就吃  我来掌勺
Yes, we'll do it tomorrow night. I'll cook!
你不觉得那样太怪了吗
Look, don't you think that would be a little weird?
怪  为什么  哪儿怪了
Weird? What? What's weird?
如果有人不喜欢墨西哥菜才是怪事
The only thing weird would be if someone didn't like Mexican food...
因为我会做法加它（一种墨西哥食物）
...because I'm making fajitas!
我非常喜欢法加它
I do like fajitas.
天呐  领养怎么这么多事儿啊
God, this adoption stuff is so overwhelming.
有跨国领养  从属领养...
There's inter-country adoption, dependency adoption.
有这么多方法
There's so many ways to go,
这就像我们一生中最大的决定
and this is, like, the biggest decision of our lives.
我咖啡里有根头发
There's a hair in my coffee.
嗨  伙计们
Hey, guys.
看见小弗兰克了吗
Have you seen Frank Jr.?
他要带着三胞胎来看我
He's meeting me here with the triplets.
太有意思了  每次你说"三胞胎"
It's funny, every time you say "triplets" ...
我马上就想到三个火辣的19岁金发女郎
...l think of three hot, blond 19-year-olds.
真有爱
That's sweet.
喝你的头发吧
Drink your hair.
这都是啥
Hey, what's all this stuff?
这些是我们从不同的领养中心找来的小册子
They're brochures from different adoption agencies.
小孩子  这个好可爱
Babies! Oh, this one is so cute.
就要这个
Get this one.
不是说要哪个就能要的
That's not really how it works.
-那怎么办的  -我不知道
- Oh, how does it work?  - I don't know!
如果你们遇到什么困难
If you're having a hard time,
可以跟我的朋友们谈谈
you should talk to my friends...
比尔和科琳
...Bill and Colleen.
他们领养了个孩子
They adopted a kid.
肯定会帮你们的
I'm sure they'd help you.
谢谢  这太好了
Thanks, that would be great.
老公  是不是很棒
Hey, honey, wouldn't that be great?
别跑...  记住我们刚说的
All right, all right. Remember what we talked about.
在公共场合  要有一定的规矩
When we're in a public place, there are certain rules.
我们不是这么说的
That's not what we talked about!
-嗨  弗兰克  -嗨
- Hi, Frank. - Hi.
-见到你真好  -我也一样
- Good to see you. - Good to see you too.
-嗨  弗兰克.  -嗨  过得怎么样
- Hi, Frank.  - Hi. Hey, how you doing?
天呐  他们都这么大了
Oh, my goodness, they've all gotten so big.
哪个是哪个啊
Which one is which again?
那个从那个女士包里
Well, that's Frank Jr. Jr...
扯出卫生棉来的是小小弗兰克
...pulling the tampons out of the lady's purse.
钱德勒在往钱德勒身上爬
And that's Chandler climbing on Chandler.
莱丝莉在往他身上扔百吉饼
That's Leslie throwing bagels at him.
想领养三胞胎吗  绝不
"Willing to adopt triplets?"  No.
我要说我们这么做是为了罗斯
Can I just say, I know we're doing this for Ross
这没啥
and that's cool.
不过如果让我来定的话
But if it was up to me,
第一次约会我们不会做这个
this is not what we'd be doing on our first date.
那么  我们会做什么
Well, what would we be doing?
我会带你出去过一个浪漫的夜晚
I'd take you out for a romantic night.
有香槟  法国大餐
Some champagne, fancy dinner,
在回家的马车上对你动手动脚
feel you up on the carriage ride home.
动手动脚
Feel me up?
在马车里
In a carriage.
-嗨  查莉  -嗨
- Hey, Charlie! - Hi.
-嗨  -嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
那么..
So...
-害怕吗  -必须的
- ...dreading this?  - Oh, you bet.
所以  你给罗斯带来点东西
So did you bring a little something for Ross?
实际上  这些是你落在我公寓的
Actually, it's some stuff you left at my apartment.
噢  谢谢
Well, thanks.
你什么时候把我的东西还给我都可以
And you can just give me my stuff whenever you want.
好  我什么都没丢掉
Yeah, I didn't throw any of that out.
我说我听到什么声音了
I thought I heard voices.
嗨  查莉
Hi, Charlie.
嗨  乔伊
Hey, Joey.
噢  你该向我介绍你的新女朋友
And, oh, you're gonna have to introduce me to your new girlfriend.
我开玩笑的  我认识瑞秋  我认识
I'm just kidding. I know Rachel. I know.
进来  请进来  进来
Come. Please come in. Come in.
好的  我们带来瓶酒
Okay. Well, we brought you some wine.
想得真周到
That is so thoughtful.
就是她别换人了
She's a keeper.
你又带来了什么
And what did you bring me, huh?
实际上  那是...
Actually, that's--
内裤  牙刷
Underwear, a toothbrush
还有范·海伦的唱片
...and a Van Halen CD.
这些我都用得着
I can use all these things!
天呐  罗斯  你看起来有点...
Gosh, Ross, you know, you seem a little--
什么  心情很好是吗  我本来就是
What? Fine? Because I am.
你呢  你呢  你呢  看到了吗
Aren't you? Aren't you? Aren't--? You see?
还有谁心情好
Who else is fine?
高兴起来
Come on.
听着  罗斯  放松一点
Listen. Why don't you try to relax.
好吗  来喝点什么
Maybe have a drink.
知道吗  这是个好主意
You know what, that is a very good idea.
我要去弄一大罐马格丽塔酒
I'm gonna go make a pitcher of margaritas.
天啊
Oh, God.
真可爱
So adorable.
看他们睡得就像天使一样
Look at them, sleeping there like angels.
对  我也很珍惜这点时间
Yeah, I really cherish these moments...
因为没多久
...because before you know it,
他们就会醒过来
they're gonna be awake again.
他们可能比较难控制
Well, they may be a handful...
-可他们真得很可爱  -是啊
- ...but they're so cute.  - Yeah.
天呐  我最后一次照看他们的时候
Oh, God, last time I babysat them,
他们最好玩了
they did the funniest thing.
我已经4年没睡觉了
I haven't slept in four years.
这么久了
That's a long time.
你不知道这有多难  菲比
You just don't know how hard it is, Phoebe.
他们太多了
There's just so many of them.
两个我还能行
You know, two I could handle.
两个就太好了  你正一手抱着一个
Two's great. You just hold one in each hand.
可第三个戴着自行车头盔
What do I do when the third one runs at me
朝我跑过来的时候怎么办
with his bike helmet on?
我又没有另一只手来保护我的要害
I got no more hands to protect my area.
他们是三个  菲比  三个
There's three of them, Phoebe. Three.
是  我知道  弗兰克
Yeah, I know, Frank.
他们从我要害出来的时候
I counted them
我数过了
when they were coming out of my area.
有时候我甚至想...
Sometimes, I think that--
不...  我不能说
Oh, no, no, no, I can't say it.
太可怕了  不
It's too horrible. No.
什么
What?
不...  我不能
No, no, I can't.
天呐  弗兰克
Oh, my God, Frank.
你想撇下他们不管
Are you thinking of leaving?
我生那三个孩子
Because I didn't have those triplets
不是用来让你遗弃的
so you could run out on them.
不  我永远不会那么做  不
Oh, no, I would never do that. No. I just...
我只是想
...was thinking that, you know,
也许你可以带走一个
maybe you could take one.
什么
What?
你不能把它们分开
You can't separate them,
这太可怕了  哪一个
that's terrible! Which one?
谢谢你能让我们来
Thank you so much for seeing us.
菲比跟我们说过
Phoebe has told us
你们人很好
great things about you guys.
我们很愿意帮忙
Please, we're happy to help.
我们领养的时候也经历过这种事
We went through the same thing when we were adopting.
所以你们家
So a lot of malfunctioning
"小弟弟""小妹妹"们都功能故障啊
wee-wees and hoo-hoos in this room, huh?
我是说  你们的家很温馨
I mean, you have a lovely home.
你们传授任何经验  我们都很感激
We appreciate anything you can tell us.
实际上  我想这个会有帮助
Well, actually, I think this might help.
这些大概就是...
It's pretty much...
你们所需要的所有信息了
...all the information you need.
噢  天呐
Oh, my God.
所有的东西都按类别分开
Everything is broken into categories,
可以对照参考
then cross-referenced.
还根据背面的颜色进行了标注
Then color-coded to correspond with the forms in the back.
太感谢了
Thank you.
我想我刚经历了一次小高潮
I think I just had a tiny orgasm.
我知道过程是让人沮丧的
I know the process is frustrating,
不过是值得的
but it's so worth it.
领养欧文
Adopting Owen was the best thing
是我们经历过得最好的事情
that ever happened to us.
太棒了  我能看看这本书吗
That's great. Can I see the book?
你想让我先洗手  是不是
You want me to wash my hands first, don't you?
这个这么漂亮  而且是白的
It's just so pretty and white.
洗手间在走廊那头  左边
Bathroom is down the hall to your left.
是我也会让他这么做
I would have told him to do it too.
我能领养你吗
Can I adopt you?
-嗨  你一定是欧文  -对
- Hey, you must be Owen.  - Yeah.
我叫钱德勒  我也当过童子军
I'm Chandler. Hey, I was in the Scouts too.
真的
You were?
当然  实际上我爸爸是童子军的女训导员
Yeah. In fact, my father was a den mother.
你知道怎么用指南针吗
You know how to use a compass?
我得过一枚徽章
I have a badge in it.
真的  太棒了
You do? That's fantastic.
你想看吗
You want to see it?
当然想
I'd love to,
不过我得先回去跟你的父母聊聊
but I gotta get back to your parents.
他们在告诉我们
They're telling us about
怎么领养你的事
how they adopted you.
什么
What?
怎么了
我是领养的
I'm adopted?
我什么都不知道
I got nothing.
第一罐马格丽塔不是太好
Well, that first batch of margaritas was not so great...
可第二罐实在太棒...棒了
...but this second batch is good.
希望到下一罐的时候
Well, maybe the next batch,
我们都能喝一点
we could all get some.
天呐  这很有趣  对吧
Oh, God, this is fun, isn't it?
就我们四个
You know, just the four of us.
就这么呆着
Just hanging.
伙计  你还好吧
Dude, are you okay?
法加它什么时候才能好
And when are the fajitas gonna be ready?
我很好  再好不过了
I'm fine, okay? I'm great.
我只是...我只是为我们而骄傲
I'm just--I'm just proud of us.
一点都不古怪
You know? There's no weirdness,
一点都不紧张
no tension.
一点都不清醒
No awareness.
我们是一个很好的"四人组"
We make a great foursome.
在一起活动应该更频繁些
We should do more stuff together.
我们去旅行吧
Let's take a trip!
好  你觉得我们应该去哪
Okay, where do you think we can go?
我的法加它
My fajitas!
听着  查莉  我只想让你知道
Look, Charlie, I just want you to know...
罗斯还需要时间
...Ross is just having a little trouble
习惯我跟乔伊在一起
adjusting to the thought of Joey and me.
他一般不这么喝酒的
You know, he normally doesn't drink like this.
这没什么
You know what, this is nothing.
我爸爸就是个疯狂的酒鬼
My father is a raging alcoholic.
对不起
I'm sorry,
让你们不舒服了
have I made this evening uncomfortable?
法加它  当心  盘子很烫
Fajitas! Be careful! Very hot plate! Very hot!
罗斯  你都没戴手套
Ross, you don't even have oven mitts on.
明天手要疼了
That is gonna hurt tomorrow.
好吧  这太疯狂了
Okay, well, this is crazy.
我们不会是在讨论
We can't seriously be talking about
把一个孩子给我  对吧
me taking one of your kids, can we?
不  当然不是
Oh, no, of course we're not.
-那简直是疯了  -是啊
- That's insane. - I know.
爱丽丝不会支持的  是吗
Alice would never go for it.Right?
我不知道  她也太累了
I don't know. She's pretty tired too.
我想她可能会同意
I think we could get her on board.
为了不起争执
Well, just for argument's sake, you know,
假设说
hypothetically...
你要放弃哪一个
...which one would you be willing to give up?
小小弗兰克
Frank Jr. Jr.?
你选了这么好的一个
You'd be getting a really good one.
他真的很幽默
He's really funny.
比如  那天他说了个笑话
Like, the other day, he made up this joke:
什么东西是绿的并且说
What's green and says,
"嗨  我是一只青蛙"
"Hey, I'm a frog"?
一只会说话的青蛙
A talking frog.
你不能带他走  他太有意思了
Oh, no, you can't have him, he's too funny.
好吧  没关系  那莱丝莉呢
Well, all right, that's fine. What about Leslie?
不...  不要是莱丝莉
Oh, no, no, not Leslie. No.
她是唯一一个会
She's the only one that knows
打着嗝说出字母表来的
how to burp the alphabet.
好吧  那就只剩下钱德勒了
All right, so that leaves Chandler.
噢不...  你不能带走钱德
No, no, you can't have Chandler.
不...  她是个小天才
No, no. She's my little genius.
我对她抱有很大期望
I got big hopes for her.
她会成为医生或者房地产经纪人
She's gonna be a doctor or a realtor.
弗兰克  已经没孩子可选了
Wow, Frank, I think we just ran out of kids.
我想你是对的
Oh, I think you're right.
菲比
Oh, wow. Phoebe,
看来我不能放弃任何一个
I don't think I can give one of them up.
我是说  他们让我发疯
I mean, you know, they drive me crazy,
可他们是我的孩子
but they're my babies.
很抱歉  弗兰克
I'm sorry, Frank,
我没想到事情会这样
I didn't realize things were so bad.
我会帮你的
You know, I'll help out more.
随时可以帮你看孩子
I can baby-sit anytime you want.
你说哪一天  我肯定会去
You name the day and I'll be there.
明天怎么样
How about tomorrow?
呃  不好
Well, that's not good.
我会推掉其它事  我会到的
But I can move some stuff around and I'll be there.
你和爱丽丝可以整天呆在一起
You and Alice just take the whole day together.
你为我们这么做
You'd do that for us?
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
你以为姐姐是干什么的
That's what sisters are for.
看看他们
Oh, look at them.
我真爱你们
I love you so much.
天呐  别醒过来...
Oh, crap, don't wake up...
比尔和科琳呢
Where are Bill and Colleen?
他们在厨房弄点吃的
They are in the kitchen, getting something to eat.
真不敢相信他们有这么好
Can you believe how nice they are?
我们必须马上走
We have to leave.
为什么  你在洗手间做了什么
Why? What did you do in the bathroom?
我还没去洗手间呢
I didn't get to the bathroom.
在路上碰到了欧文
I bumped into Owen on the way.
可他还不知道他是被领养的
He didn't know he was adopted.
有一丝丝的可能...
There's a slight chance...
我已经告诉了他
...l may have told him.
天呐  我的手袋呢
Oh, my God, where's my purse?
不  我们把东西放在这儿
No, I can replace everything in there.
- 拿上活页册  走  -嗨
- Get that binder and let's go!  - Hi.
给大家的一点小茶点
Some little snacks for everybody.
你们不用吃酸蠕虫  那是给欧文的
You don't have to eat the sour worms. Those are for Owen.
我一会儿去叫他
I'll go get him in a second.
顺便说一句   你们该知道
By the way, you should know,
我们还没告诉他他是领养的
we haven't told him he's adopted yet.
可孩子们直觉很灵敏
But kids are so intuitive.
你不认为某种程度上他已经知道了
Don't you think, on some level, he already knows?
-我是领养的  -看  直觉
- I'm adopted?  - See? Intuitive.
什么  你从哪儿听来的
What? Where did you hear that?
他告诉我的
He told me.
他还给我50块钱让我别说出来
And he paid me 50 dollars not to tell.
那现在你该把钱还给我了
Which, technically, now you should give back.
你告诉他他是领养的
You told him he's adopted?
实在对不起
I'm sorry.
可你们应该在那儿或者什么地方写明白
But You should have a sign out there or something.
或者在人们进门的时候悄悄告诉他们
Or at least whisper it to people when they come in the door.
"欧文不知道他是领养的
"Owen doesn't know he's adopted,
他也认为圣诞老人是真实存在的"
and he also thinks Santa is real."
他不存在
He isn't?
我们必须走了  亲爱的
We have to get out of here, baby.
诸位  我要向
Everyone, I would like to make a toast...
瑞秋和乔伊敬酒
...to Rachel and Joey.
还有爱情
And to love.
啊  爱情
Ah, love!
L-O-V-E  爱情
L-O-V-E. Love.
L代表"生活"
L is for "life."
没有爱情还叫什么生活
And what is life without love?
我的天呐  我们要回答吗
Oh, my God, are we supposed to answer?
O代表..
O is for...
"噢  哇"
"Oh, wow!"
V代表...
The V is for this...
事情转变得这么快
...very surprising turn of events...
而顺便说明  我完全没意见
...which I am still fine with, by the way.
E...
代表我发现
...is for how...
这是多么的正常
...extremely normal I find it...
你们俩
...that you two...
走到了一起
...are together.
有一天你们会结婚
And that one day you might get married...
还会有你们自己的孩子
...and have children of your own.
-伙计  你还好吧  -完全没问题
- Dude, are you okay? - Totally.
罗斯  你看起来不太好
Ross, you don't seem okay.
对不起
I'm sorry,
一定是招待你们的压力太大了
it must be the pressure of entertaining.
我想如果我们吃点果馅饼会感觉好点
I think everyone would feel better if we had some flan.
等等  罗斯  我...我要走了
Wait, Ross. Ross, l--I have to take off.
-不要  - 对不起
- No!  - I'm sorry.
我明天早上还有一节很早的课
I have an early class in the morning.
不过今晚很美好
But this has been lovely.
是吧  可你认为跟乔伊一起会尴尬
Wasn't it? And you thought it would be awkward with Joey.
而且你从没真正喜欢过瑞秋
And that you never really liked Rachel.
你过火了
You are on fire!
我早上给你打电话  好吗
I'll call you in the morning, okay?
-好吧  -好
- Okay. - All right.
天呐  瑞秋  罗斯刚才说得简直太...
God, Rachel, what Ross just said, that's just--
没事  女孩们从来都不喜欢我
That's okay. Girls tend not to like me.
好吧
Fine.
好吧  只上三人份果馅饼就好了
Okay. I guess it's just flan for three.
嘿  还挺押韵
Hey, that rhymes.
罗斯  我想我们也该走了
You know what, Ross, I think we're gonna take off too.
当然  天呐  我真蠢
Of course. God, I'm so stupid.
你们现在是一对了
You guys are a couple now.
我是说  你们可能想单独呆着
I mean, you probably just want to be alone.
不... 我只是说天晚了
No, it's just getting late--
没事的  真的没事
It's fine. It's totally fine.
我做了很多的马格丽塔  没事儿的
I've got plenty of margaritas. It's all good.
这又是什么好了
I don't even know what that's for.
知道吗
You know what?
我想我应该留下看他有没有事
I think I'm gonna stay here and make sure he's okay.
这可能是个好主意
That's probably a good idea.
明天早上见
I'll see you in the morning.
好吧
Okay.
乔伊
Yeah, you know, Joey, l--
我认为他永远不会
I don't think he's ever gonna
接受我们俩在一起
be okay with this.
看起来不太好  是吗
It doesn't look good, does it?
早上好
Morning.
-给你   -谢谢
- Here you go.  - Thanks.
-你整个晚上都在这儿  -对
- Did you stay here all night?  - Yeah.
是你脱了我的裤子和鞋
So you took off my pants and shoes?
不...
No...
实际上是你和着
You actually did that when you  were
《芝加哥》的原声带跳舞时自己脱掉的
dancing to the Chicago soundtrack.
听着  罗斯
Look, Ross...
关于我和瑞秋
...about Rachel and l.
你什么都不用担心
Listen, you don't have to worry about that...
因为什么都不会发生
...because nothing's gonna happen.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
我们从一开始就说
She and I said from the beginning...
如果你不接受的话
...we weren't gonna do anything
我们什么都不会做的
unless you were okay with it.
很明显...
And clearly--
你在说什么  我很好
What are you talking about? I'm fine.
没关系的  罗斯  我完全理解
It's okay, Ross. You know, I totally understand.
你当然接受不了  你们是...
Of course you're not fine. You're...
你们是罗斯和瑞秋
You're Ross and Rachel.
可现在我们不是
Yeah, except we're not.
我是说  我们已经有
I mean, we haven't been a couple in, like...
6年没在一起了
...six years.
天呐  真的吗
My God, is that right?
有这么久了
Has it been that long?
我也是这么听说的  是的
That's what I hear, yeah.
这太疯狂了  我是说  6年
This is crazy.I mean, six years...
就因为我  你们不能在一起
...and because of me, you guys aren't gonna be together?
我能问你点事吗
Can I ask you something?
说真的
Really...
你跟瑞秋到底是怎么回事
...what is this thing with you and Rachel?
别闹了  你了解我  你知道...
Come on, you know me. You know...
乔伊
Joey.
我非常喜欢她
I'm crazy about her.
她也这么想吗
And she feels the same way?
我想是的
I think so.
好吧  那么
Well, then...
可能现在我们都该往前看了
...maybe it's time we all moved on.
对  不过  罗斯  你并没有完全接受
Yeah, but, Ross, I mean, you're not okay with it, so--
不  但是我会的
No, but I want to be.
我会的
I will be.
另外  我还有查莉呢  对吧
Besides, I'm with Charlie, right?
天呐  我还跟查莉在一起呢  对吧
Oh, my God, I'm still with Charlie, aren't l?
-她没看见我跳舞吧  -没...
- She didn't see the dance, did she?  - No...
没...你只是为我一个人跳的
No, that was--That was just for me.
你...
Hey, you...?
你说真的吗
You sure about this?
对  我是说真的
Yeah, I'm sure.
那...
And...
我们的关系没问题吗
...we're okay?
-嗨  菲比  -嗨
- Hey, Pheebs. - Hey.
我们只是想给你提个醒
We just want to give you a heads up.
-比尔和科琳讨厌我们  -为什么
- Bill and Colleen hate us.  - Why?
欧文不知道他是领养的
Owen didn't know he's adopted
可莫妮卡告诉了他
and Monica told him.
什么
What?
可是  他总有一天会发现的
Still, he had to find out sometime.
可如果有人
How would you like it
告诉这三胞胎
if someone told the triplets
是你生了他们  你会高兴吗
that you gave birth to them?
我要去告诉艾玛
I'm gonna go tell Emma
生她是因为意外怀孕
she was an accident.